Albert L. Page collection of University of California, Riverside photographs UA.392
University Archives
Albert L. Page collection of University of California, Riverside photographs
circa 1954-1964
1954-1964
University Archives
Page, A. L. (Albert Lee), 1927-
UA.392
461
0.42 Linear Feet (1 box)
This collection contains portrait and group photographs of faculty from the University of California, Riverside and Citrus Experiment Station collected by Albert L. Page, an emeritus professor of environmental science and alumnus from the University of California, Riverside.
Access
This collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was acquired as a gift in 2015.
Biographical Note
Albert L. Page is an emeritus professor of environmental science and alumnus from the University of California, Riverside. His research and teaching focused on soil chemistry, ion-exchange equilibria, and biogeochemistry of trace elements. Page was also a noted member of the Soil Science Society of America (SSSA) and served as the society's president in 1996.
Collection Scope and Contents
This collection contains portrait and group photographs of faculty from the University of California, Riverside and Citrus Experiment Station. Photographs form the Biological Control, Entomology, Plant Pathology, Soil and Plant Nutrition, and Horticulture departments are included.
Collection Arrangement
This collection is arranged into two series as follows:
Series 1. Portrait photographs, circa 1954-1964
Series 2. Group photographs, circa 1954-1964
Riverside (Calif.); Photographs; University of California, Riverside. Citrus Research Center and Agricultural Experiment Station; University of California, Riverside
- Series 1. Portait photographs, circa 1954-1964; 91093
  Series Scope and Contents
  This series contains portrait photographs of faculty from the University of California, Riverside and Citrus Experiment Station.
  Series Arrangement
  This series is arranged sequentially according to box and folder number.
  - Portrait photographs of faculty from the Citrus Experiment Station at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98071 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Portrait photographs of faculty from the Department of Biological Control at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 91094 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Portrait photographs of faculty from the Department of Entomology at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98072 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Portrait photographs of faculty from the Department of Plant Pathology at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98073 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Portrait photographs of faculty from the Department of Soil and Plant Nutrition (S&PN) at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98074 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Portrait photographs of various faculty members from various departments at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98075 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series 2. Group photographs, circa 1954-1964
  This series contains group photographs of faculty from the University of California, Riverside and Citrus Experiment Station.
  - Group photographs of faculty from the Citrus Experiment Station at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98085 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Group photographs of faculty from the Department of Horticulture at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98086 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Group photographs of faculty from the Department of Soil and Plant Nutrition (S&PN) at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 98076 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Group photographs of faculty from events at UCR, circa 1954-1964; 91095 (Box 1, Folder 10)